<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FunFact.ory</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="didYouKnow">Did you know?</string>
    <string name="showNextFunFact">Show Another Fun Fact!</string>

    <!--Enter weird fun facts here-->
    <string-array
        name="funFactsList">
        <item>About 3000 years ago, most Egyptians died by the time they were 30.</item>
        <item>More people use blue toothbrushes than red ones.</item>
        <item>Your ribs move about 5 million times a year, every time you breathe.</item>
        <item>In the White House, there are 13,092 knives, forks and spoons.</item>
        <item>Slugs have 4 noses.</item>
        <item>Recycling one glass jar saves enough energy to watch TV for 3 hours.</item>
        <item>Lightning strikes about 6,000 times per minute on this planet.</item>
        <item>Owls are the only birds who can see the color blue.</item>
        <item>Thomas Edison, light bulb inventor, was afraid of the dark.</item>
        <item>During your lifetime, you\'ll eat about 60,000 pounds of food. That\'s the weight of about 6 elephants.</item>
        <item>Some ribbon worms will eat themselves if they can\'t find any food.</item>
        <item>In space, astronauts cannot cry, because there is no gravity, so the tears can\'t flow.</item>
        <item>Ostriches can run faster than horses.</item>
        <item>Ants stretch when they wake up in the morning.</item>
        <item>On average, it takes 66 days to form a new habit.</item>
        <item>Mammoths still walked the earth when the Great Pyramid was being built.</item>
        <item>Olympic gold medals are actually made mostly of silver.</item>
        <item>You are born with 300 bones; by the time you are an adult you will have 206.</item>
        <item>It takes about 8 minutes for light from the Sun to reach Earth.</item>
        <item>Some bamboo plants can grow almost a meter in just one day.</item>
        <item>The state of Florida is bigger than England.</item>
        <item>Some penguins can leap 2-3 meters out of the water.</item>
        <item>The average American drinks about 600 sodas a year.</item>
        <item>It\'s against the law to slam your car door in Switzerland.</item>
        <item>There wasn\'t a single pony in the Pony Express, just horses.</item>
        <item>Honeybees have hair on their eyes.</item>
        <item>A jellyfish is 95 percent water.</item>
        <item>In Bangladesh, kids as young as 15 can be jailed for cheating on their finals.</item>
        <item>A company in Taiwan makes dinnerware out of wheat, so you can eat your plate.</item>
        <item>The elephant is the only mammal that can\'t jump.</item>
        <item>The most common name in the world is Mohammed.</item>
        <item>Q is the only letter in the alphabet that does not appear in the name of any of the United States.</item>
        <item>America once issued a 5-cent bill.</item>
        <item>You\'ll eat about 35,000 cookies in your lifetime.</item>
        <item>Fortune cookies were actually invented in America, in 1918, by Charles Jung.</item>
        <item>A giraffe can clean its ears with its 21-inch tongue.</item>
        <item>Chewing gum while peeling onions will keep you from crying.</item>
        <item>Bats always turn left when exiting a cave.</item>
        <item>The praying mantis is the only insect that can turn its head.</item>
        <item>In Tokyo, they sell toupees for dogs.</item>
        <item>Baby robins eat 14 feet of earthworms every day.</item>
        <item>The Pentagon has twice as many restrooms as necessary. When it was built, segregation was still in place in Virginia, so separate restrooms for blacks and whites were required by law.</item>
        <item>In England, in the 1880\'s, "Pants" was considered a dirty word.</item>
        <item>Most dust particles in your house are made from dead skin.</item>
        <item>It is believed that Shakespeare was 46 around the time that the King James Version of the Bible was written. In Psalms 46, the 46th word from the first word is "shake" and the 46th word from the last word is "spear".</item>
        <item>The strength of early lasers was measured in Gillettes, the number of blue razor blades a given beam could puncture.</item>
        <item>1 pound of lemons contain more sugar than 1 pound of strawberries.</item>
        <item>All of the clocks in the movie "Pulp Fiction" read 4:20.</item>
        <item>A snail can have about 25,000 teeth.</item>
        <item>A starfish can turn its stomach inside out.</item>
        <item>During a solar eclipse the moon\'s shadow races with approximately 3.300 km/h over the Earth\'s surface.</item>
        <item>It takes an average of about 375 years to see a total solar eclipse again at a certain place.</item>
        <item>In April 2007 the German Hans-Juergen Kuhl succeeded the production of 25 million US dollars in "excellent" quality, one of the world\'s most important finds of fake money in criminal history.</item>
        <item>A crocodile can\'t stick it\'s tongue out.</item>
        <item>A shrimp\'s heart is in it\'s head.</item>
        <item>In a study of 200,000 ostriches over a period of 80 years, no one reported a single case where an ostrich buried its head in the sand.</item>
        <item>It is physically impossible for pigs to look up into the sky.</item>
        <item>Rats and horses can\'t vomit.</item>
        <item>If you sneeze too hard, you can fracture a rib.</item>
        <item>Like fingerprints, everyone\'s tongue print is different.</item>
        <item>Wearing headphones for just an hour will increase the bacteria in your ear by 700 times.</item>
        <item>Rats multiply so quickly that in 18 months, two rats could have over a million descendants.</item>
        <item>The cigarette lighter was invented before the match.</item>
        <item>A duck\'s quack doesn\'t echo, and no one knows why.</item>
        <item>Most lipstick contains fish scales.</item>
        <item>Every year about 98% of atoms in your body are replaced.</item>
        <item>Every human spent about half an hour as a single cell.</item>
        <item>Sound travels 15 times faster through steel than through the air.</item>
        <item>On average, half of all false teeth have some form of radioactivity.</item>
        <item>Only one satellite has been ever been destroyed by a meteor: the European Space Agency\'s Olympus in 1993.</item>
        <item>A chip of silicon a quarter-inch square has the capacity of the original 1949 ENIAC computer, which occupied a city block.</item>
        <item>Guinea pigs and rabbits can\'t sweat.</item>
        <item>Deer can\'t eat hay.</item>
        <item>The duckbill platypus can store as many as six hundred worms in the pouches of its cheeks.</item>
        <item>Human birth control pills work on gorillas.</item>
        <item>Gorillas sleep as much as fourteen hours per day.</item>
        <item>On average, 12 newborns will be given to the wrong parents daily.</item>
        <item>Donald Duck comics were banned from Finland because he doesn\'t wear any pants.</item>
        <item>Because metal was scarce, the Oscars given out during World War II were made of wood.</item>
        <item>Leonardo Da Vinci invented scissors.</item>
        <item>The glue on Israeli postage stamps is certified kosher.</item>
        <item>"Almost" is the longest word in the English language with all the letters in alphabetical order.</item>
        <item>A cockroach can live several weeks with its head cut off.</item>
        <item>There is a city called Rome on every continent.</item>
        <item>Camels have three eyelids to protect themselves from blowing sand.</item>
        <item>Humans and dolphins are the only species that have sex for pleasure.</item>
        <item>Polar bears are left-handed.</item>
        <item>Starfish have no brains.</item>
        <item>Butterflies taste with their feet.</item>
        <item>Humanity landed on the moon before it put wheels on it\'s luggage.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_add_new_fun_fact">addNewFunFactActivity</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
</resources>
